Finding Aid for the Colin Higgins papers, ca. 1960-1987 LSC.1560
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Gladys and Anita
  - Notes and tapes. (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Research. (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - 1988. (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - The Housewife and the Hooker, story idea; With notes and clipping., July 6, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Goat (Le Chevre)
  - [Notes]. (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Goodbye Girl
  - Final - with changes, 1976, 1977. (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Hair
  - First draft, September 20, 1974. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - First draft, - #2., September 20, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - [Hair, notes]. (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - [Hair, song book]. (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Hair work notes. (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - [Hair script]. (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - CH - Hair lyrics not in Legrt [?] script. (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - [Hair, collages, 3 folders]. (Box 126, Folder 1-3)
  - [Hair script, 1969]. (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - [Hair script, 1969]. (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - [Hair, screenplay by C. Higgins, for official eyes only, September 20, 1974]. (Box 126, Folder 6)
- Harold and Maude
  - Ballet. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Musical. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Advertising and reviews (book). (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Contracts. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Proposed book. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Aimez-vous Maude? by Edith Allaert and Jacques Bertin. (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - The rise and fall of a major studio picture ..; By Stephen P. Danforth, USC,, Cinema 466., Spring 1973 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Early notes and breakdown. (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Xerox of my first draft with Tom's comments. (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - The thesis for MFA on microfilm at UCLA Library. (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Project Three proposal - comments by Bob Kosberg, May 26, 1970. (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Original for first studio copy. (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Garwood - Goldwyn copy. (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Script - signed by C. Higgins - with note from Ross Brown. (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Script - with Mine own - revised on cover. (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Script. (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Film script - bound - interleaved with stills; With signed photographs of Bud Cort and Ruth Gordon. (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Play - bound - with stills, publicity, inscriptions; 2 volumes. (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Harold and Maude - 13 various book editions/translations. (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - [Harold and Maude, partial holograph manuscript]. (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - [Harold and Maude, test set - diagram]. (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - [Harold and Maude, partial holograph manuscript]. (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - [Harold and Maude, a new play]; Photocopied typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - [Harold and Maude, play]; Photocopied typescript with corrections. (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - [Harold and Maude, a play in two acts]; Photocopied typescript. (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - [Harold and Maude, notes and clippings on Broadway version]. (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - [Harold and Maude, a play in two acts]; Photocopied typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - [Harold and Maude, play]; Carbon copy typescript with corrections. (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Harold and Maude play, the British original. (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - [Harold and Maude, play - 1st draft synopsis, notes, etc.]. (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - [Harold and Maude, play synopsis]; Photocopied typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Harold and Maude, new notes to use. (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Redone pages of Manuscript. (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Harold and Maude novel. (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Harold and Maude clippings and old notes. (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Complete manuscript. (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Typed original manuscript. (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - [Harold and Maude, novelization, with holograph notes]. (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - [Harold and Maude novelization, galley proofs]. (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - [Harold et Maude, French play synopsis]. (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - [Harold et Maude, French play, typescript]. (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - [Harold et Maude, French play typescript, photocopy]. (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Laser video disk. (Box 147, Folder 4)
- Harold and Maude (Movie)
  - - Advertisements., 1971 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Re-release, - Advertisements., 1977, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Campaign, 1971-72. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - ad campaign - U.S., 1974 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Audit. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Foreign release awards. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Movie casting. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Computer dating. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Earnings. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Editing notes. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Fan letters. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Ruth Gordon - interviews and letters. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Bud Cort - Biography and interviews. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Colin Higgins - interviews (old). (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Lawsuit. (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Movie locations. (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Photographs. (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Press book, 1979. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Production notes. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Daily production reports. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Re-relese reviews, 1977-78. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Re-release, 1979. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Research. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Original release reviews, - U.S.A., 1971 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Press. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Minneapolis. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - French release - reviews and advertisements. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Foreign reviews. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Revival theatres cult. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Preview and Ruth Gordon birthday. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - 1st studio copy - original screenplay. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Paramount's shooting script. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Movie script. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Original screenplay - photocopy. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Original screenplay - photocopy. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Original screenplay - photocopy - Paramount cover. (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Carbons of early screenplay drafts - 2 copies; Carbon of original 1st draft and Garwood / Goldwyn copy. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Shooting schedule. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - 16mm print. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Someone to tell it to. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Television showings and Television interview clips. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Vehicles and atmosphere. (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Harold and Maude (Play)
  - France. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Japanese. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Italian language. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - South American. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - French language - Berkeley, California. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Telecast of foreign stage play. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Broadway - miscellaneous. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Broadway - partnership contract. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Broadway - publicity stills. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Broadway - Pre-show publicity. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - French version - reviews. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - U.S. - programs and reviews. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Broadway - playbill, reviews, correspondence. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Broadway - royalties. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Samuel French acting edition. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Stage rights. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - First draft. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Play. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Play - photocopy. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Play - photocopy. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Radio. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Television file. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Play - photocopy. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Broadway - theatre advertising. (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Broadway - casting and production credits. (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Broadway - casting suggestions. (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Broadway - corespondence, 1977 to present. (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, prior to 1977. (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Earnings. (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Play opening - Berlin, May 22-25, 1974. (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Edmonton, Canada. (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Trident Theatre - Quebec, Canada, September 1982. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Dutch script, program and reviews. (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Hereafter
  - [The Hereafter script]. (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - [The Hereafter, pilot script, first draft, November 1, 1972]. (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - The Hereafter, notes. (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - [The Hereafter, pilot script, second draft, December 6, 1972]. (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - [The Hereafter, episode one, script. (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - [The Hereafter, episode one, script]. (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - [The Hereafter script]. (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - [The Hereafter script, October 19, 1972]. (Box 129, Folder 11)
- Idiot's Delight
  - Idiot's Delight. (Box 134, Folder 9)
- The Ik
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - American edition of the play. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Reviews. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - [The Ik, outline for a play by C. Higgins]. (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - [The Ik script, June 26, 1974]. (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - [The Ik, notes on index cards]. (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - [The Ik, portion of script]. (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - [Les Iks, script]. (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - [The Ik, publicity, program]. (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - [The Ik, research materials]. (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - [The Ik script]. (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - The Ik - script for the play. (Box 133, Folder 3)
- Infanta
  - [Infanta, short story(?)]. (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - [Infanta, holograph notes]. (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - [Infanta, script]. (Box 135, Folder 30)
- Internal Combustion
  - By Bill C. Davis, c. 1982. (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Kanistan !!!
  - Revised 1st draft by Lawrence J. Cohen and Fred Freeman, October 4, 1982. (Box 56, Folder 7)
- The Last Request
  - [The Last Request, #5 surprise ending]; Typescript with holograph corrections and professor's comments. (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - [The Last Request]; Carbon with holograph corrections. (Box 135, Folder 11)
- Kate
  - [Expenses, memos]. (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence. (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Kate - deal memo. (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Notes. (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Colin Higgins notes on Kate. (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Handwritten notes (2 folders). (Box 78, Folder 3, 4)
  - [Research]. (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Project research. (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Catching Kate - screenplay by Jonathan Reynolds. (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Script, October 4, 1985. (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Screenplay, - with notes in margins., October 4, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Screenplay, - with notes and corrections., October 4, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Final Kate screenplay, October 7, 1985. (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - [Distribution list and script]. (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Les Patterson Saves the World
  - [Screenplay by Barry Humpries and Diane Millstead]; Sydney, 1984. (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Listen my children and you shall hear...
  - [Listen my children and you shall hear, notes]; A.k.a. Another Hero (see above). (Box 135, Folder 19)
  - [Listen my children and you shall hear, a.k.a. Another Hero]. (Box 135, Folder 34)
- Man Who Came to Dinner
  - [2 copies of play]. (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Man Who Could Work Miracles
  - [Memo]. (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Man Who Lost Tuesday
  - Final draft - copy 50. (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Final draft - copy 63. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Working copies of script - Writer's working draft,; Includes original 1st draft, June 8, 1979 May 1, 1979. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Treatment, May 20, 1985. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Treatment, May 15, 1985. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Treatment, May 20, 1985. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Treatment, May 7, 1985. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Final draft, July 7, 1979. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - First draft, - Signed by Colin Higgins., May 1, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Writer's working draft (2), - #1., June 8, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Writer's working draft (2), June 8, 1979. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Final script [empty] - contains covers only. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Final draft, July 7, 1979. (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Final draft, July 7, 1979. (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Pictures, clippings, ideas. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Location scouting trip expenses. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Local color, maps, descriptions, pictures. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Location scouting trip (2 folders). (Box 51, Folder 1, 2)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Author's outline and notes, January 2, 1979. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Colin Higgins' notes. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Notes on revisions. (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Treatment, May 20, 1985. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Final draft by Colin Higgins - #59. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Notes, - [with pages of the screenplay]., May 7, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Final draft by Colin Higgins - #47 - with notes on last page. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - 1987. (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Man who lost Tuesday script, final draft,, no.25]., July 7, 1979 (Box 121, Folder 5)
- Mermaid
  - [Screenplay]. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Breakdown - Elaine Chekich, - Confidential., September 24, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Script - N. Gan - Robert Towne - Confidential. (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Screenplays
  - Original screenplay by Don McGuire - 145pp. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Script, September 30, 1985. (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - [Magazines]. (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Money
  - [Termination of agreement]; Also known as: The pursuit of happiness. (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Revised first draft by Andy Breckman, May 1987. (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Pursuit of happiness - second draft, - Andy Breckman; Formally [formerly] `Money'., October 1987 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Pursuit of happiness - second draft, - Andy Breckman., November 1987 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Movie Ideas
  - [Racial discrimination movie]. (Box 135, Folder 32)
  - [Notes for unidentified script]. (Box 135, Folder 36)
- Nine to Five
  - [1 poster]. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - [Office set, 3 plans]. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advertising. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Advertising - flyer. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Effects on labor and other industries. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - AFI observer - John Rome. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Animation. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Animation cells. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Academy Award nominations. (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Award nominations - no Academy. (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Budget. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Buttons. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Calendars. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Call sheets. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Casting. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Women. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Eddie. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Men. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - For review. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Casting lists. (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Staff and crew. (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Cast list. (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Casting. (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Deals. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Earnings. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Editing notes. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Fan letters. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Foreign posters and programs. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Gag reel. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Locations. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Looping and wild lines. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Music. (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Fantasy opticals. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Paperback book and novelization. (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Photographs ordered for Colin. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Post-production schedule. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Insert shooting. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Possible bell tower - Europe shooting. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - First draft, - photocopy., September 20, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 5, 7)
  - First draft, - in blue binder., September 20, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Script, n.d.. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Second Draft, November 9, 1979. (Box 43, Folder 9, Box 44)
  - Second draft, September 9, 1979.
  - Numbered draft, November 14, 1979. (Box 44, Folder 2, 3)
  - Numbered draft, - Janet Daube copy., November 14, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Numbered draft, - 110., November 14, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Numbered draft, - corrected and renumbered., November 14, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Final draft, December 12, 1979. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Script, December 10, 1979. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Reviews #2 (2 folders). (Box 45, Folder 3, 4)
  - Sale of film to other media. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Crew screening lists. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Screenings. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Draft script - distribution. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - WGA - arbitration on writing credits. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Script by Patricia Resnick, October 28, 1978. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - First revised draft - Patricia Resnick, December 1, 1978. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - First revised draft - Patricia Resnick, December 22, 1978. (Box 46, Folder 2-4)
  - Script notes. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Script supervisor's script. (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Script timing. (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Treatment - first version. (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Treatment - pages. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Treatment, August 13, 1979. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Treatment, - photocopy., August 13, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Treatment - revised original, August 16, 1979. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Script, September 6, 1979. (Box 47, Folder 5, 6)
  - Script, - With additional ending pages., September 7, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Script, - No blue pages, not final., December 12, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Script, - No blue pages., December 12, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Final draft, - #173., December 12, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Final draft,; With inscription, Dear George and Janet, Merry Christmas.., December 12, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Shooting schedule[s], - 1 copy; - 3 copies; With correspondence., December 21, 1979 January 2, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - One line schedule. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - 16mm prints. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Storyboards. (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Television file. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Theatre bookings. (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Main and end titles. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Videocassettes. (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Press kit (folder 1 of 2). (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Premiere. (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Pre-production. (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Previews. (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Production. (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Production reports. (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Programs for the film. (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Press kit - another copy (folder 2 of 2). (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - New York Times Sunday Magazine article. (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Private Benjamin - screenplay [empty]; Nine to Five also on label. (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Promotion. (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Props. (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Publicity. (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Dallas press junket, November 20, 1980. (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Dolly Parton interviews. (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Research. (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - [Nine to Five, bound scrapbook]. (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - [Nine to Five, bound photo album]. (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - [Nine to Five production schedule]. (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - [Nine to Five, production script (?)]. (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - [Nine to Five, production schedule and notes]. (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - [Nine to Five calendar, 1981]. (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Final draft by Colin Higgins, December 12, 1979. (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Nine to Five - novelization. (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Blow up photographs and cartoon poster. (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Nine to Five - Storyboards, Violet's fantasy, Judy's fantasy; Hospital sequence and Hart's transformation. (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Photographs - 15 items (folder 1 of 7). (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Photographs - 20 items (folder 2 of 7). (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Photographs - 20 items (folder 3 of 7). (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Photographs - 20 items (folder 4 of 7). (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Photographs - 20 items(folder 5 of 7). (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Photographs - 20 items (folder 6 of 7). (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - Photographs - 21 items (folder 7 of 7). (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - Laser video disk. (Box 147, Folder 5)
- Office
  - [Plans, 7 items]. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Opera
  - [Opus One, script]; Typescript with holograph corrections and notes. (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - [Opus 101, stream of conciousness #4]; Typescript with professor's comments. (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - [Opus #103, #6]; Typescript with professor's comments. (Box 135, Folder 10)
- Out on a Limb
  - Script revisions. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Screenplay - part one - first draft,; Revised, August 11, 1985 August 29, 1985. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Screenplay - part two - first draft,; Photocopy., August 23, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Screenplay - part two - first draft,; Typescript (carbon) copy. Annotated., August 23, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Script breakdown - minifile - Colin Higgins. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Chapter breakdown - Gerry's scenes - holograph notes; In folder with Shirley MacLaine on the cover. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Early script - part one. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Early script - part two. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Script pages - part one - continuations of revisions; With manuscript notes interleaved., August 30, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Script notes. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Script notes - Colin Higgins. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Script - Joan Tewkesbury. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Shooting schedule. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Staff and crew lists. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Standards and practices. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Travel. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Writers Guild award entry form, July 1987. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Script pages - part one - revised, September-November 1985. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Part two - first draft, - revised, August 23, 1985 September 4-October 18, 1985. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Book breakdown. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Call sheets. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Cast list. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Casting. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Casting - London. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Day out of days. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Locations. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Location pictures. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Looping. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Memoirs - Colin Higgins. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Peru. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Publicity - general. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Publicity - London. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Publicity - Peru. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Publicity - Stockholm. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Registration. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Research. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - The Teaching of Ambres. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook - [loose clippings in a flat box]. (Box 13, Folder unknown container)
  - Script - Part one, revised; With Part 2, revised, August 29, 1985 - October 7, 1985 September 4-October 5, 1985. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Script - Bob's trims, October 28, 1985. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Script - part one - revisions, August 29, 1985-January 27, 1986. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Script - revised pp.105-106 - with memo. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Script - part one - revisions, August 29, 1985-January 10, 1986. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Script - part two - revised, September 4, 1985-January 10, 1986. (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Out on a Limb, Harold and Maude
  - Publicity and promotional material. (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Outward Bound
  - Revised first draft by Barry Schneider. (Box 81, Folder 1, 2)
- Paradise on Main Street
  - Musical comedy by Richard Baskin - revised draft, February 20, 1985. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Revised draft by Richard Baskin, - with sketches; This copy signed by Colin Higgins., February 27, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Outline and new pages, - with correspondence., December 21, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Revised draft, - with memos, correspondence., April 21, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Deal memo. (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Locations. (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Revised draft, July 1984. (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Submitted Universal, February 27, 1985. (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Revised draft, June 18, 1985. (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Revised draft, June 25, 1985. (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Revised draft, - master., July 11, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Revised draft screenplay, October 24, 1985. (Box 82, Folder 3, 4)
- Personal
  - [Reiki healing materials, certificate]. (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - [Christmas cards, 1987]. (Box 109, Folder 4, 5)
  - [Address book]. (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - [Yearly inventory, 1986]. (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - [Yearly inventory, 1987]. (Box 110, Folder 3, 4)
  - [Journal of dreams, July 5-August 29]. (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - [Miscellaneous]. (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - [Realia -pins]. (Box 110, Folder 7)